[APPLAUSE]
♪♪
♪ I heard he sang a good song, I
heard he had a style ♪
♪ And so I came to see him to
listen for a while ♪
♪ And there he was, this young
boy, a stranger to my eyes ♪
♪ Strumming my pain with his
fingers ♪
♪ Singing my life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
song ♪
♪ Killing me softly
with his song ♪
♪ Telling my whole life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
song ♪
♪ I felt all flushed with fever,
embarrassed by the crowd ♪
♪ I felt he'd found my letters
and read each one out loud ♪
♪ I prayed that he would finish,
but he just kept right on ♪
♪ Strumming my pain with his
fingers ♪
♪ Singing my life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
song ♪
♪ Killing me softly
with his song ♪
♪ Telling my whole life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
song ♪
♪ He sang as if he knew me in
all my dark despair ♪
♪ And then he looked right
through me as if I wasn't there♪
♪ And he just kept on singing,
singing clear and strong ♪
♪ Strumming my pain with his
fingers ♪
♪ Singing my life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
song ♪
♪ Killing me softly
with his song ♪
♪ Telling my whole life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
song ♪
♪ Woahhh-oh-oh-oh-ohhhhhh ♪
♪ La la la la la oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Laaaaaaaa ♪
♪ La-ah-ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Strumming my pain ♪
♪ Yeah, he was singing my life ♪
♪ And killing me softly with his
song ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
♪ Telling my whole life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly ♪
♪ He was strumming my pain with
his fingers ♪
♪ And singing my life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
song ♪
♪ Killing me softly
with his song ♪
♪ Telling my whole life with his
words ♪
♪ Killing me softly with his
song ♪
[APPLAUSE]
Thank you very much.